http://www.centerragold.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Centerra is very respectful about the privacy concerns of the users of this website. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from users. However, certain non-personal information of users is recorded by the standard operation of this website‘s servers. This information is primarily used to provide an enhanced online experience for the user. Information tracked includes the type of browser being used by the user, the type of operating system in use by the user and the domain name of the user's Internet service provider. By having this information, web pages optimized for a particular user's computer are automatically available to that user. Other uses of this information include internal review of the number of users of this website but only in an aggregate and non-personally identifiable form. E-mail addresses and other personally identifiable data about users of this website are known only when voluntarily submitted. This information is used to better understand users‘ use of this website. Centerra sometimes also uses e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information to contact users who communicate with us. For example, Centerra may direct e-mail to users who provide us with their e-mail addresses for specific purposes such as inquiries.
Any material, information or other communication (including questions, comments or suggestions) you transmit to Centerra through this website will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary ("Communications"). In making any such transmission, you agree that Centerra will have no obligations of any kind with respect to the Communications. Where it is necessary, in order to answer your inquiry, the Communications you have provided may be passed to any Centerra office or affiliate worldwide. By sending any Communications to us, you are consenting to the personal information contained therein being transferred within Centerra and being processed by Centerra for these purposes. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from Centerra any unlawful, threatening, libellous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or other materials that violate any law.
This website places a "cookie" in the browser files of a user‘s computer. This is how the website “remembers” a user’s previous visit. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. The cookie could enable Centerra to relate a user‘s use of this website to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided.
Corporate
Quick Facts
Centerra Values
Strategy and Objectives
Directors & Management
Corporate Governance
History
Quick Links
Centerra Gold?
Copyright © 2020 Centerra Gold Inc.
Powered by
Renmark Financial Communications Inc.
